Guide to the Ambassador Auditorium Collection ARS.0043
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Series 10: Concert Recordings, 252 boxes (266.2 linear ft.)
  - Audio Open Reel Tapes and Cassettes
    - Concert Recordings 8422-8427:, 03-17-1984 -- 03-31-1984; 11 10 1/2" open reel tapes (Box 494)
      (8424:1-2) Ofra Harnoy, Gold Medal Cello Series; Yves Henry, piano, 03-19-1984: Locatelli, Pietro Antonio, 1695-1764. [unspecified] Adagio in D minor -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Sonatas, violoncello, piano, no. 1, op. 38, E minor -- Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946. Vida breve. Danza, no. 1 -- Granados, Enrique, 1867-1916. Danzas españolas. Oriental -- Popper, David, 1843-1913. Elfentanz -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Introduction et polonaise brillante -- Franck, César, 1822-1890. Sonatas, violin, piano, A major; arr. -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Gershwin, George, 1898-1937. Porgy and Bess. Summertime
      (8425:1-2) Jakob Gimpel, piano, 03-24-1984: Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 18, op. 31, no. 3, E♭ major -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Sonatas, piano, no. 3, op. 5, F minor -- Toch, Ernst, 1887-1964. [Title from program:] Profiles, Op. 68 -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Andante spianato et Grande polonaise brillante
      (8426:1-2) Lucia Popp, soprano; Irwin Gage, piano, 03-25-1984: Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Knabe -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Gebüsche -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Fluss -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Schmetterling -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. [Title from program:] Rose, D. 745 -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Fülle der Liebe -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. An mein Herz -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Jüngling an der Quelle -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. [Title from program:] Liebende schreibt, D. 673 -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Einsame -- Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Lieder, op. 2. Selections -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 67. Heft 1 -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 37. Mein Auge -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 37. Meinem Kinde -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 10. Zeitlose -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 10. Verschwiegenen -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 36. Hat gesagt--bleibt’s nicht dabei -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 10. Allerseelen -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. An Sylvia -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Seligkeit
      (8427:1) Zamfir, pan flute, 03-31-1984: [see program listing after Tape 8427:2]
      Gage, Irwin; Harnoy, Ofra; Gimpel, Jakob; Zamfir, Gheorghe; Popp, Lucia; Nosal̕, Štefan; Montoya, Carlos; Henry, Yves; Lúčnica (Dancing ensemble)
    - Concert Recordings 8427-8432:, 03-31-1984 -- 04-09-1984; 11 10 1/2" open reel tapes (Box 495)
      (8427:2) Zamfir, pan flute, 03-31-1984: [see program listing after Tape 8428:1-2]
      (8428:1-2) Zamfir, pan flute, 04-01-1984: Musical introduction -- [Name and title from program:] Papadiamandis. Nausicaa -- Vangelis. Chariots of fire -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. [unspecified] Aria -- Trandafir crescut in apa -- Zamfir, Gheorghe, 1941- Doïna de jale -- Mocirita cu trifoi -- Rumanian medley -- John, Elton. Your song -- Sus pe cul mea dealului -- Briul Oltenesc -- Introduction -- Hora din Muntenia -- Doina Oltului -- Fantasy for cymbalum -- Joel, Billy. Just the way you are -- Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Kinderscenen. Träumerei -- Zamfir, Gheorghe, 1941- Danny’s night -- Lennon, John, 1940-1980. Yesterday (1965) -- Improvisation on Rumanian themes -- Dinicu, Grigoraș. Hora staccato
      (8429:1-2) Peter Donohoe, Gold Medal Piano Series, 04-02-1984: Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Jeux d’eau -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Gaspard de la nuit -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Masques -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Isle joyeuse -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 3, op. 55, E♭ major; arr. -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Preludes, piano, op. 23. No. 4 -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Waltzes, piano, op. 64. No. 2
      (8430:1-2) Philip Jones Brass Ensemble, 04-04-1984: Susato, Tielman, fl. 1529-1561. Danserye. Selections; arr. -- Salzedo, Leonard. [Title from program:] Diferencias for brass ensemble, Op. 95 -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Piano music. Selections; arr. -- Bull, John, d. 1628. King’s hunt; arr. -- Farnaby, Giles, ca. 1565-1640. [Title from program:] His dreame - a toye; arr. -- Byrd, William, 1542 or 3-1623. March before the battle; arr. -- Crosse, Gordon. Peace -- Langford, Gordon. London miniatures -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Dushkin, Samuel, 1891-1976. Siciliana, violin, piano; arr. -- Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908. Skazka o t︠s︡are Saltane. Nu, teperʹ, moĭ shmelʹ;arr. -- Hoffnung, Gerard. [From listing on container:] Galop for post horns
      (8431:1-2) Beaux Arts Trio, 04-05-1984: Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Trios, piano, strings, K. 548, C major -- Smetana, Bedřich, 1824-1884. Trio, piano, strings, op. 15, G minor -- Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847. Trios, piano, strings, no. 1, op. 49, D minor -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Trios, piano, strings, op. 90, E minor. Andante moderato, quasi tempo di Marcha
      (8432:1-2) Ridge String Quartet, Gold Medal Chamber Series, 04-09-1984: Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Quartets, strings, H. III, 48, F major -- Bartók, Béla, 1881-1945. Quartets, strings, no. 4 -- Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Quartets, strings, B. 92, E♭ major -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Delibes, Léo, 1836-1891. [Title from listing on container:] Roi s’amuse. Passepied; arr.
      Philip Jones Brass Ensemble; Donohoe, Peter; Zamfir, Gheorghe; Beaux Arts Trio; Ridge Quartet
    - Concert Recordings 8433-8437:, 04-26-1984 -- 05-07-1984; 11 10 1/2" open reel tapes (Box 496)
      (8433:1-3) An evening with Karl Haas featuring the Viennese classics, a piano recital with commentary, 04-26-1984: Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Sonatas, piano, H. XVI, 49, E♭ major -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Fantasien, piano, K. 475, C minor -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Allegrettos, piano, WoO 53, C minor -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Rondos, piano, op. 51. No. 1 -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Variationen über ein Thema aus dem Finale zum 2. Akt der Oper La fiera di Venezia von Antonio Salieri -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 2, op. 2, no. 2, A major -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 8, op. 13, C minor. Adagio cantabile
      (8434:1-2) I Musici; Pina Carmirelli, violin, 04-28-1984: Wassenaer, Unico Wilhelm, graaf van, 1692-1766. Concerti armonici. N. 1 -- Tartini, Giuseppe, 1692-1770. Concertos, violoncello, string orchestra, A major -- Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Concertos, violins (2), string orchestra, RV 523, A minor -- Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Estro armonico. N. 4 -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, harpsichords (3), string orchestra, BWV 1064, C major; arr. [Encore, from program listing on container:] Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. [unspecified]
      (8435:1-2) Little Ambassadors of Shanghai; Cao Shun-quin, director, 05-04-1984: [see program listing after Tape 8436:1-2]
      (8436:1-2) Little Ambassadors of Shanghai; Cao Shun-quin, director, 05-05-1984: [program selected from works by the following:] Nie, Er, 1912-1935 -- Ma Sheng-long -- Jin Yue-ling and Pen Xiu-Wen -- Wusimanjian, Pu Qi-zhang and Shi Wu-jie -- Hu Deng-tiao -- Bo Lan-gu and Cheng Jin-yuan -- Foster, Stephen Collins, 1826-1864 -- Jiang, Guoji -- Li Zong-wang -- Liu, Tianhua, 1895-1932 -- Huang, Haihuai -- Meiliqige, Zhang Xiao-Feng and Gui Xi-Li -- Gui Xi-Li -- Gao Hua-xin -- Wang, Huiran -- Lou Shu-hua -- Wang, Changyuan -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912 -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828 -- Ma Yao-zhang and Li Zhong-han -- Couperin, François, 1668-1733 -- Dimitrescu, Constantin -- Weber, Carl Maria von, 1786-1826 -- Ouyiang Qian-shu and Xiao Ming -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849 -- He, Luting -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809 -- Grieg, Edvard, 1843-1907
      (8437:1-2) Claudio Jaffe, cello; Young Musicians Foundation Debut Orchestra, Neal Stulberg, conductor, Gold Medal Cello Series, 05-07-1984: Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Concerti grossi, violins (2), violoncello, string orchestra, op. 6. No. 5 -- Ives, Charles, 1874-1954. Symphonies, no. 3 -- Shostakovich, Dmitriĭ Dmitrievich, 1906-1975. Concertos, violoncello, orchestra, no. 1, op. 107, E♭ major
      Musici; Haas, Karl; Young Musicians Foundation. Debut Orchestra; Stulberg, Neal; Jaffe, Claudio; Carmirelli, Pina
    - Concert Recordings 8438-8443:, 05-09-1984 -- 06-11-1984; 11 10 1/2" open reel tapes (Box 497)
      (8438:1-2) Danish National Orchestra; Sixten Ehrling, conductor; Robert McDuffie, violin, 05-09-1984: Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Romeo et Juliette (Fantasy-overture) -- Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847. Concertos, violin, orchestra, op. 64, E minor -- Nielsen, Carl, 1865-1931. Symphonies, no. 3, op. 27 -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Nielsen, Carl, 1865-1931. Maskarade. Overture
      (8439:1-2) American Youth Symphony; Mehli Mehta, director/conductor; Endre Balogh, violin, 05-13-1984: Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Meistersinger von Nürnberg. Vorspiel -- Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich, 1865-1936. Concertos, violin, orchestra, op. 82, A minor -- Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Symphonies, no. 5, op. 64, E minor
      (8440:1-2) Court Revels of the Consortium Antiquum; Angene Feves and Charles Perrier, Renaissance Dancers, 05-15-1984: Prelude -- Dowland, John, 1563?-1626. [unspecified] Pavan -- Simpson, Thomas, 1582-1628? [Title from program:] Alman -- Coperario, John, ca. 1570-1626. [unspecified] Fantasia -- Gastoldi, Giovanni Giacomo, fl. 1582-1609. [Title from program:] Il ballarino -- Caroso, Fabritio. Nobiltà di dame. [Title from program:] Bellezze d’Olimpia -- Ortiz, Diego, ca. 1525-ca. 1570. [Title from program:] Gamba, galliard -- Almande [anonymous] -- Infelice, balletto [anonymous] -- Caroso, Fabritio. Nobiltà di dame. Laura suave -- Bataglia, balletto [anonymous] -- Gastoldi, Giovanni Giacomo, fl. 1582-1609. [Title from program:] Il ballarino, allemande -- Bartlet, John, fl. 1606-1610. Booke of ayres. Of all the birds that I do know -- Mundy, John, d. 1630. Robin -- Simpson, Thomas, 1582-1628? Bonny sweet Robin -- Praetorius, Michael, 1571-1621. Terpsichore. Ballet des coqs -- Praetorius, Michael, 1571-1621. [Title from program:] Canarie -- Eyck, Jacob van. Fluyten lust-hof. English nightingale -- Bartlet, John, fl. 1606-1610. Booke of ayres. Pretty duck there was -- Woodicock [anonymous] -- Turkeylony [anonymous] -- Chirping of the lark -- Scandello, Antonio, 1517-1580. [Title from program:] Little White Hen -- Like as the lark within the Merlin’s foot -- Cornysh, William, d. 1523. A Robyn, gentyl Robyn -- Byrd, William, 1542 or 3-1623. Volta
      (8441:1-2) United States Coast Guard Band; Lt. Lewis J. Buckley, director, 05-16-1984: Star-spangled banner (Song); arr. -- Sousa, John Philip, 1854-1932. Hail to the spirit of liberty -- Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Outdoor overture -- Reed, Alfred. Rushmore -- Ibert, Jacques, 1890-1962. Concertino da camera. Larghetto-Animato molto; arr. -- Fillmore, Henry, 1881-1956. Circus bee -- Holst, Gustav, 1874-1934. Planets. Mars -- Fillmore, Henry, 1881-1956. Klaxon -- Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Circus polka -- Coast Guard Dixieland Jazz Band selections -- King, Karl, 1891-1971. Barnum & Bailey’s favorite -- Berlin, Irving, 1888-1989. [Title from program:] Tribute to Irving Berlin; arr. -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Sousa, John Philip, 1854-1932. Stars and stripes forever -- Before the mast (nautical medley)
      (8442:1-2) Jai Jeffryes, Gold Medal Piano Series, 06-04-1984: Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Rondos, piano, K. 485, D major -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Andantes, musical clock, K. 616, F major; arr. -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Gigues, piano, K. 574, G major -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 31, op. 110, A♭ major -- Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Blumenstück -- Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Toccata, piano, op. 7, C major -- Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Arabesque, piano, op. 18, C major -- Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981. Sonatas, piano, op. 26 -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Etudes, piano, op. 10. No. 8
      (8443:1) Pasadena Young Musicians Orchestra; Richard Rintoul, conductor; Tedd Joselson, piano, 06-11-1984: [see program listing after Tape 8443:2]
      Joselson, Tedd; Statsradiofoniens symfoniorkester (Copenhagen, Denmark); United States Coast Guard Band; American Youth Symphony; Buckley, Lewis J.; Feves, Angene; Mehta, Mehli; Perrier, Charles; Ehrling, Sixten; McDuffie, Robert; Jeffryes, Jai
    - Concert Recordings 8443-8448:, 06-11-1984 -- 10-02-1984; 11 10 1/2" open reel tapes (Box 498)
      (8443:2) Pasadena Young Musicians Orchestra; Richard Rintoul, conductor; Tedd Joselson, piano, 06-11-1984: Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Rodeo. Saturday night waltz -- Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Rodeo. Hoe-down -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Serenades, orchestra, no. 1, op. 11, D major -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Concertos, piano, orchestra, no. 5, op. 73, E♭ major
      (8444:1-2) Blomstedt Institute Symphony Orchestra, 07-05-1984 [NB: program listing on container is dated 07-11-1985 and does not match printed program; both tape reels are labeled 07-05-1984]: Weber, Carl Maria von, 1786-1826. Freischütz. Ouverture -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Symphonies, H. I, 86, D major -- Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Symphonies, no. 8, op. 88, G major
      (8445:1-2) Dimitris Sgouros, piano, 07-18-1984: Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. [unspecified], F major -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Ballades, piano, no. 1, op. 23, G minor -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Ballades, piano, no. 4, op. 52, F minor -- Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Episoden aus Lenau’s Faust. Tanz in der Dorfschenke -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Variationen über ein Thema von Paganini -- Balakirev, Miliĭ Alekseevich, 1837-1910. Islameĭ
      (8446:1-2) Sabicas, guitar, 09-23-1984: Costa del sol -- Campanitas -- Huelva -- Sentimiento gitano -- Murallas de Cádiz -- Canto a Linares -- Variaciones de alegrías -- Guadalquivir -- Inspiración -- Semana Santa en Sevilla -- Cadencia gitana -- Caña de Azúcar -- Arabia -- Homenaje a Jerez -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Sabatiado -- Sitro de Saracos -- Malagueña -- Variations
      (8447:1-2) Montserrat Caballé, soprano; Miguel Zanetti, piano, 09-24-1984: Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Giulio Cesare. Piangerò la sorte mia -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Giulio Cesare. Se pietà di me non senti -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Nuits d’été à Pausilippe. Crépuscule -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Amor marinaro -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Inspirations viennoises. Zingara -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Betly. In questo semplice modesto asilo -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Adelia. [Title from program:] Ecco a tuoi piedi io cado -- Paladilhe, Emile, 1844-1926. Psyché -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Rossignol -- Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. [Title from program:] Serenade: Ah, quand je dors -- Mompou, Federico, 1893-1987. Combat del somni -- Serrano, José, 1873-1941. Canción del olvido. Canción del olvido -- Luna, Pablo, 1879-1942. Niño judío. De España vengo -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] [Name and title from container:] Galvez, J.M. Variante de Petener -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Trittico. Gianni Schicchi. O mio babbino caro -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Bohème. Sì, mi chiamano Mimì -- Cilèa, Francesco, 1866-1950. Adriana Lecouvreur. Io son l’umile ancella
      (8448:1-2) Beaux Arts Trio, 10-02-1984: Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Trios, piano, strings, K. 564, G major -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Trios, piano, strings, no. 1, op. 18, F major -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Trios, piano, strings, op. 97, B♭ major -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. [unspecified] Final movement from trio in A Major
      Blomstedt, Herbert; Joselson, Tedd; Zanetti, Miguel; Sgouros, Dimitris; Sabicas; Caballé, Montserrat; Beaux Arts Trio
    - Concert Recordings 8449-8454:, 10-28-1984 -- 11-11-1984; 11 10 1/2" open reel tapes (Box 499)
      (8449:1-2) The Best of Gilbert and Sullivan with the Stars from the D’Oyly Carte Opera Company; Kenneth Sandford, bass-baritone; Vivian Tierney, soprano; Lorraine Daniels, mezzo-soprano; Geoffrey Shovelton, tenor; Alistair Donkin, baritone; David Mackie, piano, 10-28-1984: Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. Princess Ida. [Title from program:] Woman of the wisest wit -- Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. Princess Ida. [Title from program:] Would you know the kind of maid -- Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. Iolanthe. Selections -- Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. H.M.S. Pinafore. Selections -- Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. Yeomen of the Guard. Were I thy bride -- Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. Yeomen of the Guard. [Title from program:] Hereupon we’re both agreed -- Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. Mikado. Selections -- Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. Patience. Selections -- Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. Sorcerer. Selections -- Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. Pirates of Penzance. Selections -- Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. Gondoliers. [Title from program:] Once more gondolieri
      (8450:1-2) Pilar Lorengar, soprano; Jeffrey Goldberg, piano, 11-03-1984: Cesti, Antonio, 1623-1669. Orontea. Vieni, Alidoro, vieni -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Così fan tutte. Come scoglio -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Gesänge aus Wilhelm Meister. Lied der Mignon (No. 4) -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Fischerweise -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Junge Nonne -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Rastlose Liebe -- Wolf, Hugo, 1860-1903. Mörike-Lieder. Gesang Weylas -- Wolf, Hugo, 1860-1903. Mörike-Lieder. Verlassene Mägdlein -- Wolf, Hugo, 1860-1903. Goethe-Lieder. Mignon -- Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Zigeunermelodien -- Granados, Enrique, 1867-1916. Tonadillas. Maja dolorosa -- Granados, Enrique, 1867-1916. Tonadillas. Mirar de la maja -- Granados, Enrique, 1867-1916. Canciones amatorias. Selections -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Granados, Enrique, 1867-1916. Tonadillas. Majo discreto -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 10. Zueignung -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Trittico. Gianni Schicchi. O mio babbino caro
      (8451:1-2) Eduardo Fernández, guitar, 11-04-1984: Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764. Pièces de clavecin (1724). Villageoise; arr. -- Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764. Pièces de clavecin (1724). Tambourin; arr. -- Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord. Selections; arr. -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Partitas, BWV 997, C minor; arr. -- Tosar Errecart, Héctor A. (Héctor Alberto), 1923-2002. Gandhara -- Villa-Lobos, Heitor. Etudes, guitar -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946. Sombrero de tres picos. Danza del molinero
      (8452:1-2) Stephen Bishop-Kovacevich, piano, 11-07-1984: Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 30, op. 109, E major -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 31, op. 110, A♭ major -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 32, op. 111, C minor -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Moments musicaux. No 6
      (8453:1-2) Guarneri String Quartet, 11-08-1984: Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Quartets, strings, K. 458, B♭ major -- Suk, Josef, 1874-1935. Meditace na staročeský chorál "Svatý Václave" -- Webern, Anton, 1883-1945. Sätze, string quartet, op. 5 -- Turina, Joaquín, 1882-1949. Oración del torero -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Quartet, strings, F major -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Quartets, strings, op. 41. No. 1. Adagio
      (8454:1) Nathan Milstein, violin; George Pludermacher, piano, 11-11-1984: [see program listing after Tape 8454:2]
      Shovelton, Geoffrey; Tierney, Vivian; Guarneri Quartet; Milstein, Nathan; Donkin, Alistair; Daniels, Lorraine; D'Oyly Carte Opera Company; Sandford, Kenneth; Pludermacher, Georges; Kovacevich, Stephen; Goldberg, Jeffrey; Fernández, Eduardo; Mackie, David; Lorengar, Pilar; Sullivan, Arthur; Gilbert, W. S. (William Schwenck)
    - Concert Recordings 8454-8459:, 11-11-1984 -- 11-29-1984; 11 10 1/2" open reel tapes (Box 500)
      (8454:2) Nathan Milstein, violin; George Pludermacher, piano, 11-11-1984: Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Sonatas, violin, continuo, RV 10, D major; arr. -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonaten und Partiten, violin, BWV 1001-1006. Partita, no. 1 -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 3, op. 108, D minor -- Paganini, Nicolò, 1782-1840. Caprices, violin, M.S. 25. No. 11 -- Paganini, Nicolò, 1782-1840. Caprices, violin, M.S. 25. No. 5 -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Nocturnes, piano, op. 27. No. 1; arr. -- Mussorgsky, Modest Petrovich, 1839-1881. Shvei︠a︡ -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Introduction et rondo capriccioso -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Consolations. [unspecified] -- Mussorgsky, Modest Petrovich, 1839-1881. Gopak (Song)
      (8455:1-2) Orchestra of the 18th Century; Frans Brüggen, director/conductor, 11-13-1984: Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787. Don Juan. Selections -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, harpsichord, string orchestra, BWV 1053, E major; arr. -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 1, op. 21, C major
      (8456:1-2) Judith Blegen, soprano; Håkan Hagegård, baritone; Martin Katz, piano, 11-15-1984: Wolf, Hugo, 1860-1903. Italienisches Liederbuch. Selections -- Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Puisqu’ici-bas -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Romances, voice, piano (1891). Ame évaporée -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Pastorale -- Duparc, Henri, 1848-1933. Phidylé -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. D’un cœur qui t’aime (Duet) -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Don Pasquale. [Title from program:] Basta. Ho capito -- Lehár, Franz, 1870-1948. Lustige Witwe. Selections -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Ach varmland dy skona [traditional] -- Grieg, Edvard, 1843-1907. Peer Gynt. Solvejgs sang -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Don Giovanni. Là ci darem la mano
      (8457:1-2) Concert Royal; James Richman, artistic director/harpsichord; Sandra Miller, associate director/flauto traverso; with members of the New York Baroque Dance Company; Catherine Turocy, artistic director/choreographer, 11-27-1984: Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Brandenburgische Konzerte. Nr. 5 -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Suites, orchestra, BWV 1067, B minor. Ouverture -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Pastor fido (1734). Terpsichore